<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Charles Palmer</title>
	<atom:link href="/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>I like learning, teaching, and playing with technology that does those things.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 22:42:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.5.4</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2024/06/cropped-site-logo-icon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>Charles Palmer</title>
	<link>/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Hello World!</title>
		<link>/blog/hello-world/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Charles Palmer]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 16:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miscellaneous]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=218</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Hello there!&#160; I am up and running with my new site here for my personal/professional portfolio and associated blog. Now that I’ve got it up and running, I figure I should go back and add a few initial articles to explain how I got here! The starting place is that I have recently been “impacted” [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Hello there!&nbsp; I am up and running with my new site here for my personal/professional portfolio and associated blog. Now that I’ve got it up and running, I figure I should go back and add a few initial articles to explain how I got here!</p>



<p>The starting place is that I have recently been “impacted” at my job, meaning that I no longer have that job. This has got me thinking about my future and the potential need to look for jobs outside of my current company. Since I have no real presence outside my current company today, it’s time to create one.</p>



<p>This site will act as a place for me to store projects and serve as a portfolio should I seek jobs externally. Additionally, I want to start sharing my innovations and recording them in a more public format so that others in my industry can hopefully learn from me. I believe I have something valuable to share!&nbsp; So whether you&#8217;re here as a potential employer, or as a fellow L&amp;D professional, welcome!</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
